# UNC COMPUTER SCIENCE MAJOR

- 919-656-7462
- ≥ aszala@cs.unc.edu
- linkedin.com/in/aszala/github.com/aszala
- % <u>aszala.com</u>

## ABOUT ME

Seven years of web and application development experience. Many awards at hackathons. Research Assistant at the MURGe-Lab (UNC-NLP Group).

Strong programming skill in Python, Java, C#, C, JavaScript, and HTML/CSS. Experienced with Machine Learning, AWS, GCP, IBM Cloud, Docker, Unity, Node.JS, Git/GitHub, 3D modeling, and animation. Expert certified in Excel.

## EDUCATION

## Computer Science Major (B.S.)

UNC Chapel Hill Class of 2023

## Statistics and Analytics Minor

UNC Chapel Hill Class of 2023

## PUBLICATIONS

Research paper titled, "ArraMon: A Joint Navigation-Assembly Instruction Interpretation Task in Dynamic Environments", accepted into EMNLP Findings. https://arxiv.org/abs/2011.07660

## COURSEWORK

- Java Programming
- Special Topics in Computer Science
- System Fundamentals
- Data Structures
- Computer Organization
- Models of Languages and Computation
- Calculus I, II, III
- Discrete Mathematics

## EXPERIENCE

## **Summer Intern 2020 (May – August)**

Interned at the MURGe-Lab (UNC-NLP Group) research lab. Developed an AI model to interpret natural language instructions and carry out robotic action tasks. Model was built in Python using PyTorch and a simulation environment was built in Unity with C# and hosted on AWS. Research paper accepted into EMNLP Findings.

## **Undergraduate Research Assistant** 2019 – Present

Researching new ideas and directions for Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Machine Learning at the MURGe-Lab (UNC-NLP Group). Primarily focused on integrating NLP with other fields of research such as Computer Vision and Embodiment.

## TSA President 2018 – 2019 TSA Member 2015 – 2019

Software developer and leader at the school Technology Student Association (TSA). I have won several awards from TSA.

#### Webmaster 2018 - Present

Created and maintain the following websites using HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript/jQuery

- Personal website portfolio aszala.com
- TSA webmaster aszala.com/2019-webmasters

#### Game and Application Developer 2014 - Present

Developed several games and applications.

- AI for presentations that won NCSU Packhacks Hackathon 2019
- AI virtual assistant using Python, OpenCV, TensorFlow, and IBM Watson
- Developed many games from scratch in Java and using Unity with C#
- Developed my own Game Engine in Java capable of making 2D games with many advanced features such as mesh collisions, particle systems, and ray tracing